What a Feeling
First when there's nothing but a slow glowing dream that your fear seems to hide deep inside your mind
All alone
I have cried silent tears full of pride in a world made of steel made of stone
Well I hear the music close my eyes, feel the rhythm
Wrap around take a hold of my heart
What a feeling being's believing
I can have it all now
I'm dancing for my life
Take your passion and make it happen
Pictures come alive you can dance
Right through your life
Now I hear the music
Close my eyes,
I am rhythm
In a flash it takes hold of my heart
What a feeling being's believing
I can have it all now
I'm dancing for my life
Take your passion and make it happen
Pictures come alive now
I'm dancing
Through my life
What a feeling
What a feeling being's believing
Pictures come alive you can dance
Right through your life
What a feeling
I can have it all
Have it all oh oh oh ooh oh oh
What a feeling being's believing
Hey hey hey hey hey hey
What a feeling